<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>software on Hugo Belin</title>
    <link>https://hugobelin.com/tags/software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in software on Hugo Belin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 23:01:28 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hugobelin.com/tags/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Next Presentation Pop with Tableau</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/software/animatedviz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 23:01:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/software/animatedviz/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents Make your next meeting pop and instead of using a boring PowerPoint presentation (nothing against PowerPoint 😅) give it a try to a Tableau dashboard! Let&amp;rsquo;s make it even more fun by adding some animations to capture your audience atention. For this example I&amp;rsquo;m going to use a Super Mario Bros style Tableau dashboard. I will show how to build one using several tools
Plan Your Presentation The first step seems obvious but also takes some planning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make your own Photo Viz</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/software/photoviz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:51:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/software/photoviz/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents Dust off your photo archive and put it to work! In this post I&amp;rsquo;m going to show you how to take your photos into a basic Tableau dashboard that will have them located in a map. This map will show where those photos were taken allowing you to group them and see significant events by location and optionally over time
We will also review options for hosting your photos in a way that can be embed-able and useful for our Tableau dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
