<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>site on Hugo Belin</title>
    <link>https://hugobelin.com/categories/site/</link>
    <description>Recent content in site on Hugo Belin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:40:11 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hugobelin.com/categories/site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Link Tree</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/linktree/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:40:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/linktree/</guid>
      <description>Promoted Content  Mexican Lottery Game on NFT   Mexican Lottery Game on NFT created using pixel art  read more      Hike Collection   Tableau Dashboard that contains my hikes with pictures over the time  read more      Photo Collection   All my photos in a map. With the help of this Tableau Dashboard I&amp;#39;m locating them in a map that helps visualize them  read more      2019 Mukilteo and Diablo Lake   Details about the weekend used to visit the Mukilteo Lighthouse as well as a boat tour on the Diablo Lake  read more      Trip to San Diego 2019   A short trip to visit for first time San Diego in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 21:04:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/resume/</guid>
      <description>We are all a masterpiece in progress. We are all capable of great things. As such I strive to create excellent software that creates delightful experiences for end users. I am a Software Engineer based on the Seatle Area, you can find out more about my career history in my LinkedIn Profile . Every now and then I contribute with Vizzes to Tableau Public , this website as well as few others (such as BrewingCats ) that I maintain are hosted in GitHub (here my profile ) or in GitLab .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telemetry</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/telemetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 17:29:37 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/telemetry/</guid>
      <description>Most if not every website uses some form of telemetry. Since the inception of this website I had also plans for adding telemetry to it. The thing is for many sites, the data generated by users is collected not only with the purpose of improving the website, detect usability issues, or ways to improve it in general, many sites sell this data and use it for other purposes. Since I don&amp;rsquo;t plan to make use of this data for purposes other than improve this website I&amp;rsquo;m taking few steps to ensure the data handling is transparent</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brewing Cats Core</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/brewingcatscore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 22:19:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/brewingcatscore/</guid>
      <description>This website is created over a common core which is used for other websites. It packs specific features and functionality that make HugoBelin.com a better site. Brewing Cats Core augments the base functionality from the Ananke Theme which is built using Hugo framework
This post showcases the completed work as well as the upcoming features. These can be tracked in the following Coda board:
Loading…  (() = { let paramStyle = &#39;max-width:100%;&#39;; let styles = paramStyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 21:15:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>This website is a forked version built by Brewing Cats (my own company) using a set of reusable components (both code libraries, services, and content) that I call Brewing Cats Core. My website as well as the core component roadmaps are shown below:
 Loading…  (() = { let paramStyle = &#39;max-width:100%;&#39;; let styles = paramStyle.split(&#39;;&#39;); for (let i = 0; i  BrewingCatsCore.Logger.traceInfo( `iframe Component`, &#39;component.iframe&#39;, &#39;tagId_15&#39;, &#39;ComponentSetup&#39;, { &#39;component&#39;: &#39;iframe&#39;, &#39;src&#39;: &#39;https:\/\/coda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 18:00:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/credits/</guid>
      <description>This post was created to recognize the hard work of the many developers that made this site possible thus far. From hosting, to frameworks, they&amp;rsquo;re recognized here:
Hosting, Libraries, Frameworks and other Technologies Loading…  (() = { let paramStyle = &#39;max-width:100%;&#39;; let styles = paramStyle.split(&#39;;&#39;); for (let i = 0; i  BrewingCatsCore.Logger.traceInfo( `iframe Component`, &#39;component.iframe&#39;, &#39;tagId_15&#39;, &#39;ComponentSetup&#39;, { &#39;component&#39;: &#39;iframe&#39;, &#39;src&#39;: &#39;https:\/\/coda.io\/embed\/bNNCG5bcPs\/_suqXw?viewMode=embedplay\u0026hideSections=true&#39; } );  
 Image Credits: Unsplash: Circuit Board image by @harrisonbroadbent    Image Credits: Main Page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 22:58:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Hugo Belin and this is my personal website. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for my resume and professional history you can find it on this Resume post
Just another human being in this planet trying to leave it better than when I arrived 
This is my internet footprint:
  Facebook   Twitter   Instagram   Snapchat   Reddit   Tableau Public   LinkedIn   I own and run BrewingCats as a side project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 21:23:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/changelog/</guid>
      <description>This post contains a list of the changes made to the website, it is used for tracking purposes
  Website Version Core Library Version Release Name     4.23.30          Ben Solo         (() = { document.querySelector(&#34;.accb39c2b1b9bd7d16ed9a04ab968175b&#34;).innerHTML = `${BrewingCatsCore.Config.Version}`; })();   Versioning Policies Major.Minor.Build  | | |_______ Brewing Cats Core Version  | |_____________ New features  |___________________ Official new releases (Tied to a Release name)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policy</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 17:34:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/policy/</guid>
      <description>Terms of Use Do the good and not the evil. Use of this website imply that you agree with the terms of use stated below. That being said Brewing Cats operates with certain amounts of data which are used in different ways to improve the functionality of the website as well as to enable interoperability with other sites on the web. The data being generated due to its use will be used in a fair and transparent way, we believe that the data generated by a single user can help us make a better website by improving, optimizing, and allowing us to know the key investments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
