<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo Belin</title>
    <link>https://hugobelin.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hugo Belin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 22:31:51 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hugobelin.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thank You Tableau</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/uncategorized/thankyoutableau/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 16:28:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/uncategorized/thankyoutableau/</guid>
      <description>Move to the Web Team
Thank You Tableau Almost 6 years have passed since I joined Tableau back in 2016. What an adventure! Amazing company, amazing coworkers, great place for learning. I had the responsibility of improving parts of the product (go Web Authoring!) as well as its test infrastructure. I worked in multiple Tableau conferences (Austin, TX 2016. Las Vegas, NV 2017. Las Vegas, NV 2019) and had a lot of fun, both during the event and after.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Privacy Screen</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/uncategorized/diyscreen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 11:40:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/uncategorized/diyscreen/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents Getting ready for the summer! One of the things that just needed to be done before we could enjoy the company of guests in the backyard was the addition of a privacy wall in the deck. We got our hands dirty for few days and accomplished it! Some woodwork here, some staining there (plus few tools) was all we needed to call this project done. Here&amp;rsquo;s how it happened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Link Tree</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/linktree/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:40:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/linktree/</guid>
      <description>Promoted Content Mexican Lottery Game on NFT Mexican Lottery Game on NFT created using pixel art read more Hike Collection Tableau Dashboard that contains my hikes with pictures over the time read more Photo Collection All my photos in a map. With the help of this Tableau Dashboard I&amp;#39;m locating them in a map that helps visualize them read more 2019 Mukilteo and Diablo Lake Details about the weekend used to visit the Mukilteo Lighthouse as well as a boat tour on the Diablo Lake read more Trip to San Diego 2019 A short trip to visit for first time San Diego in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 21:04:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/resume/</guid>
      <description>We are all a masterpiece in progress. We are all capable of great things. As such I strive to create excellent software that creates delightful experiences for end users. I am a Software Engineer based on the Seatle Area, you can find out more about my career history in my LinkedIn Profile . Every now and then I contribute with Vizzes to Tableau Public , this website as well as few others (such as BrewingCats ) that I maintain are hosted in GitHub (here my profile ) or in GitLab .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest Reads</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/uncategorized/tweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:07:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/uncategorized/tweets/</guid>
      <description> Tweets by hugobelinm Image Credits: Unsplash: Road Trip with Raj image by @roadtripwithraj Scroll to Top Site Views: 0 Page Views: 0 Your Site Views: 0 Your Page Views: 0 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telemetry</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/telemetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 17:29:37 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/telemetry/</guid>
      <description>Most if not every website uses some form of telemetry. Since the inception of this website I had also plans for adding telemetry to it. The thing is for many sites, the data generated by users is collected not only with the purpose of improving the website, detect usability issues, or ways to improve it in general, many sites sell this data and use it for other purposes. Since I don&amp;rsquo;t plan to make use of this data for purposes other than improve this website I&amp;rsquo;m taking few steps to ensure the data handling is transparent</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make your own Photo Viz</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/software/photoviz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:51:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/software/photoviz/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents Dust off your photo archive and put it to work! In this post I&amp;rsquo;m going to show you how to take your photos into a basic Tableau dashboard that will have them located in a map. This map will show where those photos were taken allowing you to group them and see significant events by location and optionally over time
We will also review options for hosting your photos in a way that can be embed-able and useful for our Tableau dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hike Collection</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/travel/hikecollection/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 20:48:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/travel/hikecollection/</guid>
      <description>The map below has the places of my documented hikes (according to my photo archive). I plan to update this as I go on more hikes so make sure to check here every now and then. The Tableau dashboard below shows the location, date, and title of each hike on a map
Hike Collection
Site Views: 0 Page Views: 0 Your Site Views: 0 Your Page Views: 0 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Collection</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/travel/photocollection/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 23:39:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/travel/photocollection/</guid>
      <description>This post summarizes my collection of photos all of which are spread across multiple posts in this website and more, while individual posts point to specific places from the world which is more convenient for visualizing smaller portions of land and interacting with the viz. Having all of the photos in one place make it nice to see all the places I&amp;rsquo;ve been to and bring memories back 😃
You can check out the viz directly on Tableau Public Image Credits: Unsplash: Flighting image by @wistomsin Site Views: 0 Page Views: 0 Your Site Views: 0 Your Page Views: 0 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 Mukilteo and Diablo Lake</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/travel/2019mukilteodiablolake/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 14:16:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/travel/2019mukilteodiablolake/</guid>
      <description>Starting the weekend on July 27 we decided to visit the Mukilteo Lighthouse. Surprisingly after being several years in the region we&amp;rsquo;ve never visited this lighthouse before so we decided to head over there and take a look at it
Main View from the Lighthouse, Ferry
Mukilteo lighthouse and ferry
Construction of the lighthouse began on 1905 and became operational in 1906. They used a &amp;lsquo;revolving Fresnel lens&amp;#39; same that is on exhibition below along with a white bust sculpture from George Vancouver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip to San Diego 2019</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/travel/2019sandiego/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 20:24:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/travel/2019sandiego/</guid>
      <description>A simple, short trip to San Diego. A good opportunity to get to know another nice place from US. Off we go early on Saturday we got a chance to catch the late morning in San Diego, first walk: downtown San Diego, close to Gaslamp Quarter. Doing an initial assessment of the surroundings
Downtown First View
My initial thought about the city was &amp;rsquo;new meets old&amp;rsquo;, I had this idea reinforced throughout the trip&amp;hellip; new buildings next to old ones over and over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of Play</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/gaming/stateofplay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 15:42:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/categories/gaming/stateofplay/</guid>
      <description>In the table below I&amp;rsquo;m showing the games I&amp;rsquo;m currently playing, the games I&amp;rsquo;ve finished, the games I will be playing, as well as the games I&amp;rsquo;m considering. In the future I will add links to reviews to those games 🎮
Loading… Gamer Card DarthOguh Xbox: DarthOguh PlayStation: HugoBelin Nintendo: darthoguh Steam: DarthOguh Twitter, Instagram, Website Latest Gaming Status Tweets by DarthOguh Scroll to Top Site Views: 0 Page Views: 0 Your Site Views: 0 Your Page Views: 0 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brewing Cats Core</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/brewingcatscore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 22:19:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/brewingcatscore/</guid>
      <description>This website is created over a common core which is used for other websites. It packs specific features and functionality that make HugoBelin.com a better site. Brewing Cats Core augments the base functionality from the Ananke Theme which is built using Hugo framework
This post showcases the completed work as well as the upcoming features. These can be tracked in the following Coda board:
Loading… Scroll to Top Site Views: 0 Page Views: 0 Your Site Views: 0 Your Page Views: 0 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 21:15:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>This website is a forked version built by Brewing Cats (my own company) using a set of reusable components (both code libraries, services, and content) that I call Brewing Cats Core. My website as well as the core component roadmaps are shown below:
Loading… Loading… Credits: Photo by airfocus on Unsplash Scroll to Top Site Views: 0 Page Views: 0 Your Site Views: 0 Your Page Views: 0 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 18:00:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/credits/</guid>
      <description>This post was created to recognize the hard work of the many developers that made this site possible thus far. From hosting, to frameworks, they&amp;rsquo;re recognized here:
Hosting, Libraries, Frameworks and other Technologies Loading… Image Credits: Unsplash: Circuit Board image by @harrisonbroadbent Image Credits: Main Page. Unsplash: EMP Museum image by @sakulich Site Views: 0 Page Views: 0 Your Site Views: 0 Your Page Views: 0 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 22:58:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Hugo Belin and this is my personal website. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for my resume and professional history you can find it on this Resume post
“Be yourself; everyone else is already taken.” ― Oscar Wilde This is my internet footprint:
Facebook Twitter Instagram Snapchat Reddit Tableau Public LinkedIn GitHub GitLab I own and run BrewingCats as a side project. You can see my contributions in GitLab , GitHub and my Gists Favorite Movies and Series Loading… Favorite Videogames Loading… Gamer Card DarthOguh Xbox: DarthOguh PlayStation: HugoBelin Nintendo: darthoguh Steam: DarthOguh Twitter, Instagram, Website Image Credits: Unsplash: Note image by @noemieke Scroll to Top Site Views: 0 Page Views: 0 Your Site Views: 0 Your Page Views: 0 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 21:23:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/changelog/</guid>
      <description>This post contains a list of the changes made to the website, it is used for tracking purposes
Website Version Core Library Version Release Name 4.29 @@@ Versioning Policies Major.Minor.Build | | |_______ Brewing Cats Core Version | |_____________ New features |___________________ Official new releases (Tied to a Release name)
Milestone Naming Conventions Milestone names are taken from:
List of Star Wars characters then: Star Wars Legends characters then: Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic characters Release milestone would look like:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policy</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 17:34:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/site/policy/</guid>
      <description>Terms of Use Do the good and not the evil. Use of this website imply that you agree with the terms of use stated below. That being said Brewing Cats operates with certain amounts of data which are used in different ways to improve the functionality of the website as well as to enable interoperability with other sites on the web. The data being generated due to its use will be used in a fair and transparent way, we believe that the data generated by a single user can help us make a better website by improving, optimizing, and allowing us to know the key investments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagram</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 12:08:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/instagram/</guid>
      <description>This plugin has been deprecated
Instagram-Auto-Embed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embed</title>
      <link>https://hugobelin.com/posts/embed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugobelin.com/posts/embed/</guid>
      <description>Loading...</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
